gfoundries.com 2017-02-25

# Privacy Policy

**GLOBALFOUNDRIES Privacy Overview**

GLOBALFOUNDRIES is committed to respecting your privacy. In general, you can visit [www.globalfoundries.com](http://www.globalfoundries.com/) without revealing any information about yourself. GLOBALFOUNDRIES and its analytic vendor does collect information regarding visitors to our Web site, such as domain name, number of visits,and average time spent to measure use and improve the content of our site. We analyze this data for trends and statistics to help us provide you with better service. Our Web site may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites. GLOBALFOUNDRIES is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of third party web sites. 

**Personal Information**

There are times when we may request information from you, such as your, name, address and e-mail address. When additional information is requested, we will try to let you know at the time of collection how we intend to use the personal information you provide, such as respond to your inquiry, participate in certain promotions, conduct a survey or allow you to access specific information. We do our best to maintain the accuracy of any personal information you do supply to us. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We may transfer or otherwise disclose information we collect from site visitors to employees and independent contractors of GLOBALFOUNDRIES, analytic vendors, and other service providers and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for GLOBALFOUNDRIES. We will also transfer or otherwise disclose information we collect from site visitors in response to judicial process, and, as permitted under applicable provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on a matter related to public safety. Except as noted above, information we collect from site visitors will not be shared with individuals or other companies unrelated to, or that do not perform a business, professional or technical function for, GLOBALFOUNDRIES. 

**Security and Quality**

GLOBALFOUNDRIES is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the individual identifying information that you provide. You can help GLOBALFOUNDRIES update and maintain the accuracy of any personal information you supply by notifying GLOBALFOUNDRIES of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. 

**Cookies, Web Beacons & Other Tracking Technologies**

GLOBALFOUNDRIES uses cookies to allow us to understand what areas of our Web site are of interest to you so we can better serve and provide you with tailored information from our Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. These cookies do not track individual information, but rather record Web site traffic anonymously. 

Some GLOBALFOUNDRIES Web sites may also use "Web beacon" technologies. When a visitor accesses pages on the GLOBALFOUNDRIES Web site with a Web beacon, an anonymous notice of that visit is generated which may be processed by us or by our vendors. These Web beacons work in conjunction with cookies to let us know what portions of our site are of interest to our visitors and to help us provide you with tailored information from our web site. 

If you turn off cookies, Web beacon technologies will still detect anonymous visits, but the notices they generate cannot be associated with other anonymous information or personally-identifiable information and are disregarded. 

**Enforcement of this Statement**

If you have questions regarding this Statement, you should first contact [privacy.global@globalfoundries.com](mailto:privacy.global@globalfoundries.com). In most cases we respond to your inquiries within a 24-hour time period. 

**Changes to this Statement**

GLOBALFOUNDRIES will occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Statement. For material changes to this Statement, GLOBALFOUNDRIES will notify you by placing prominent notice on this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed of how GLOBALFOUNDRIES is helping to protect your information.

**Oversight or Questions**

GLOBALFOUNDRIES welcomes comments and questions on this policy. As stated above, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy and will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Due to the rapidly evolving changes on the Internet, we may update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this page.

Last updated: 04 March 2009
